[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLANE ROARING]
♪ Fly me to the moon ♪
♪ And let me play
among the stars ♪
♪ Let me see
what spring is like ♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars ♪
♪ In other words,
please be true♪
♪ In another words♪
♪ I...♪
♪ I love♪
♪ You♪
♪ You, you, and you♪
The three of us?
MAN: Let's give it up
for Rich.
That one never gets old.
He's talking to me not you.
WOMAN 2: Beautiful voice,
Captain.
So good.
[RICH CHUCKLES]
You are terrible.
You know what I'm terrible at?
Marriage.
I'm pretty good
at first dates.
[WOMEN LAUGHING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hey, honey.
NADINE: Oh, thank God.
I thought we missed you.
I got your message.
Yeah, they changed the roster.
When are you coming back?
Babe, I'll send you
a new schedule when I get it.
[SIGHS] Ben,
I know you're hurting.
We both are.
But you can't keep
running away from that.
Hold on, babe.
Hey, Lisa,
you found me something.
LISA:
There's a LA-Shanghai route,
but I don't know,
it's leaving soon.
All right, I'll take it.
You won't have time
to go home.
Doesn't matter. I'll take it.
Hey, I got Nadine
on the other line.
I'll call you back, all right?
Honey?
SEAN: Mom, where are you?
NADINE: Our son is sick, Ben.
He needs you here.
Oh, I gotta go.
SEAN: Mom!
Nadine...
NADINE: Sean's calling.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER PA]
Ow.
Sir? You can't smoke here.
Cinemas, planes, bars.
Now I can't even smoke outside
without being harassed
by the fun police.
Come on.
Sir.
The designated smoking areas
are located right over there.
[GROANS] Fuck!
BEN: Hey, Rich.
It looks like I'm your
right seat to Shanghai.
Been a while.
BEN: I heard
you're hanging it up.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Penny...
Hey.
...you missed karaoke night.
I hear you sang
that same song again.
Damn. Did it work?
It always works.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thank you.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Sorry, sir,
please step this way.
Hell.
I've got a random.
Meet you guys at the gate.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
BEN: How you doing, Penny?
PENNY: Good. How are you?
You trust me
to captain a plane.
You worried about
my toothpaste.
Any batteries or power banks?
Sir?
Uh, no.
Sure I can't get upgraded?
I'm a gold member, you know.
GIRL: I don't want to.
You know
how I get with flying.
Okay, look,
do we have to do this here?
GIRL: I don't want to.
Right here? Tell you what.
GIRL: You don't get it.
MAN: The plane is bigger
to Shanghai...
GIRL: No, they're not.
MAN: ...than the ones you've
previously been on. Okay?
That's something, right?
You folks okay?
Yeah, it's fine. My daughter
doesn't like flying.
You know what's more dangerous
than flying on an airplane?
Hippos.
No way. You made that up.
Google it.
You're gonna be fine.
Unless someone smuggles
a hippo onboard.
Are you, like, a captain?
No, I'm a first officer.
It's my job to make sure
the captain flies straight.
Aren't you too old
not to be a captain?
MAN: Cora!
[LAUGHS]
Tough, huh?
Yeah.
Uh, well, Cora...
sometimes in life...
you gotta take a few detours
to get where you're going.
You ever had to take a detour?
No, I'm extremely punctual.
Good girl.
[CHUCKLES] She's tough.
I know, thank you.
BOY: Cora.
Cora, Cora, Cora, look.
Look what Mama got me.
Hey, guys.
Look, look.
CORA: Could that thing
be any louder?
I know. Cool, right?
And I got
a new battery for this.
Okay, there we go.
Just put a pet chip
in his neck.
Uh...
WOMAN: Cora, do you mind?
I was doing something.
I'll give it back.
Just hang on.
The password's his birthday.
Listen, Cora, honey,
we're gonna need you
to look out for your brother
on this trip, okay?
Step-brother.
MAN: That's it.
That's the last of this.
Load it up.
STAFF: Thank you.
WOMAN OVER PA:
Northeastern Airlines
Flight N-140 to Shanghai
will now begin boarding.
MAN: Hey, hey!
Don't you dare
puke on me, bro.
I'll drop your
drunk ass right here.
I'm not playing, Hutch.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
HUTCH: [IN ENGLISH]
Oh gosh, Esports.
Playing video games
isn't a real sport.
It's a bunch of losers
kicking it in Mommy's basement
with bags of Doritos and...
Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Ooh. What's up, Esports?
Let go.
Get your hands off her!
Whoa. Okay. Sorry.
He's just a little drunk.
Ooh! She's feisty. I like it.
Don't touch her.
What are you
gonna do about it,
Captain Keyboard?
Hutch, get your disrespectful
dumbass in line.
Is this how we talk to a lady?
Coach, I got this--
Shut up, Jesse.
Now, this is not how
we represent ourselves
on my team.
My apologies, Miss.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Excuse you.
I should have been upgraded.
Re-circ fan is written up.
We can't legally depart
until they fix it.
[BEEPS]
RICH: I just reset it.
Doesn't mean it won't
crap out again later.
Hi. Welcome.
Just to the right.
You made us wait long enough.
What's up, bro?
Yeah, okay. There we go.
Yeah. Here you can...
Hey, I'm fine.
Let's sit down.
Come on. Let's sit down.
MAN: You want to strap in?
PENNY ON PA:
Good afternoon, passengers.
My name is Penny,
and on behalf
of Northeastern Airlines,
I'd like
to welcome you aboard...
Coming through. Excuse us.
And don't let us interrupt.
Sorry. We were never here.
KATIE: Sir, would you please
put your seat back up?
Why sure.
I would like to welcome you
aboard Flight N-140...
What's your social media?
...departing from LAX
and arriving at Shanghai.
Thank you.
PENNY: We'll be beginning
our departure
procedures shortly.
So, at this time,
please take your seats,
and make sure your seat belts
are securely fastened.
ATC: Northeastern 140,
you will depart today
from runway 24-L.
BEN: Before Takeoff Checklist.
Flaps.
Where do you think
they're set?
I just need a response.
You do know, Ben,
that the FAA has us
confirm flaps over and over
only because those idiots
flying Delta 1141
were so busy yakking about
which flight attendant
they wanted to bang,
they forgot to check them.
Captain,
I just need a response.
Flaps are five, Ben.
Same place as the last
three times we checked them.
ATC: Northeastern 140,
you are cleared
for takeoff, 24-L.
Clear for takeoff 24 left,
Northeastern 140.
[ENGINE ROARING]
[INTERCOM BEEPS]
See you guys.
Captain.
It looked like you wanted
to take a swing at me
over that flap check.
That wouldn't help
my career any.
Isn't that how you got
bounced out of the Air Force?
Well, that senior officer
had it coming.
You, you're just,
you're annoying.
Blew your pension
and your benefits.
That's tough with a wife
and young kids.
Had to catch on with some
shitbag commuter airline
and now you're
in that seat when,
of course,
you should be in mine,
and thinking you can't afford
to break any more rules.
Well, Ben,
[SCOFFS]
I'm sure not gonna tell.
So I could have popped you one
and gotten away with it?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I'd rat you out.
BEN: I know you would.
No ice? Mmm-hmm.
What's up?
Not a lot.
My granddaughter
lives in Shanghai.
Awesome.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[CHUCKLES]
Ben, um, [CLEARS THROAT]
I just wanted to check in
on how your son's doing.
Heard he's been
pretty sick lately.
Must be tough on your wife,
especially when
you're working and all.
Yeah, well,
Nadine's family lives nearby.
They help out when I'm gone.
[WHISPERS] What the fuck?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[GASPS] Oh, damn it.
Statistics say that turbulence
has never brought
a plane down.
Is that supposed
to be comforting?
I'm fine. I just
spilled my gin and tonic
when I really need it most.
[MAN SNORING]
[BUTTON BEEPS]
Hi, sir.
Hey, take a guess what I need.
I'm sorry.
We're out of earplugs.
That's perfect.
Just perfect.
What, you're gonna ration out
the toilet paper, too, huh?
You guys are unbelievable!
Sir, you can't do that!
I can't hear you.
Yeah.
What?
Way out of your league.
Oh, no. No, I wasn't.
[CHUCKLES] Wait. Really?
She's a solid nine.
Hate to break it to you,
but you're a five.
Maybe you could
scrub up to a six,
but that's being generous.
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
I'm getting destroyed
by Betsy Ross back here.
Wait, what if I've got
a great personality?
You don't.
Oh.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES]
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Cora, honey.
Look, I know change
is scary, okay?
But Finn really
looks up to you.
So would it kill you
to be just a little nicer?
[CORA GAGS]
Hey, it's me.
[SIZZLING]
Cora.
Where's Mom and Dad?
They went to the pool
for a swim.
There's a pool on the plane?
Yeah. Yeah, it's back there.
Hey, little man,
can't you find your seat?
Oh, you into gaming, huh?
Right. You wanna
show me how it's done?
Yeah? Come on. Here.
Okay. Your right hand
is right here...
[BEEPING]
I am canceling master warning
for forward cargo fire.
Confirm.
Confirmed.
Let's do the memory items
forward cargo fire.
Copy that.
Forward cargo fire switch on.
Confirm.
Confirmed.
Fire bottle discharge on.
Confirm.
Confirmed.
[HISSING]
[RATTLES]
BEN: Pan, pan, pan.
Northeastern 140.
We have a fire indication
in our forward cargo bay
and smoke has been detected.
We require a heading
to the nearest
suitable airport,
Northeastern 140.
MAN: Northeastern 140,
this is KZAK Oakland.
Your nearest airport
is Guam International.
Four hundred
nautical miles south.
Let's get the captain
back here.
Roger.
BEN: Roger, KZAK.
Northeastern 140.
We are now direct Guam
descending at 10,000 feet,
Northeastern 140.
You okay, honey?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Ben, what do we have here?
Forward cargo fire.
We've completed
the memory items.
Fire bottles
aren't discharging.
I've declared an emergency.
We're descending to 10,000,
redirecting
to Guam International.
Get down there. Put it out.
Roger.
Dad?
Dad? Are you in there?
[RUMBLING]
[GASPS]
The fire turned
into an explosion.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
What the hell?
We lost the cabin.
This isn't getting any better.
Taking her down.
Come on! Come on, grab them.
Put it on, come on.
Put this on. Okay?
Rich, put your mask on.
Ben, we're gonna
be level at 10,000
before you can
even get that on.
PENNY: Zoe, get your mask!
11,000, for 10,000.
Thousand to go.
Level 10,000.
BEN: I see 10,000.
We're stable.
Instruments responsive.
Take the aircraft.
I'm gonna make a PA.
My aircraft. Confirmed.
Your aircraft. Confirmed.
Folks, this is
the captain speaking.
We have a fire
in the cargo hold.
We've descended
to a safe altitude
and diverted
to Guam International Airport.
It's very important that
everybody remain calm.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm coming straight back.
RICH:
We need all of you to follow
your flight
attendant's instructions...
One second.
...as we get passengers near
the affected area
moved to safer seating.
Lisa.
There are more seats
at the back!
This way, sir!
Go, go!
No, no! Don't move
unless you have to!
Lisa!
Clear the passage!
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] My parents!
Not now. Stay here.
[PANTING]
We've lost engine one.
Sir, you can't do that!
You're worried about this?
Get back to your seat
right now!
Flight controls don't respond.
Hydraulics are gone.
Don't tell me what's broken.
Tell me what still works
on this jet.
You have manual cables
to the outboard ailerons,
elevator and rudder.
Let's get to it.
BEN: Mayday, Mayday, Mayday!
Northeastern 140.
We lost engine one.
MAN: 140, Guam International
is still the closest option.
We need something closer.
140, we have nothing.
You're over open ocean.
MAN: Help us! Help!
[RATTLING]
Instrument needles
all rolling back to zero.
We're on standby instruments.
RICH: Mayday, Mayday, Mayday!
This is Northeastern 140.
We've lost power.
Captain, we lost the radio.
Stop the APU.
Roger.
It's okay. Just hold on, okay?
RICH: Hit it again.
BEN: Nothing.
Again!
APU is not coming up.
We're at 6,000 feet.
Try manual deployment of RAT.
Ram Air Turbine. Confirmed.
Ram Air Turbine working.
Instrument's back online.
Relight the engine.
BEN: Ignition.
Hit it again.
LISA: No!
Dad! Where are you?
No, no, no.
Wait, wait. Come here.
Let me go! Let me go!
We'll be all right.
RICH: Try it again.
It's not working.
We don't have enough
airspeed to relight.
And no breathing room
to dive for more.
We're gonna ditch.
Start dumping the fuel.
We're giving up
on the relight?
Do it! Do it now!
Dumping fuel.
RICH: This is
the captain speaking.
Brace for impact.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
STEWARDS: Brace! Brace!
Heads down! Stay down!
Brace! Brace! Heads down!
Okay, okay.
Get down! Get down!
[SPEAKING MAORI]
RICH: [IN ENGLISH] Ben,
I want altitude and airspeed
callouts every thousand feet.
3,000 feet, airspeed 220.
RICH: Too damn fast.
I have a visual reference
to swells.
We gotta come right.
Rich, the checklist says we
just parallel with the swells.
Swells aren't that bad.
I want all the headwind
I can get
to slow vertical down rate.
Rich, if we go wing low
and catch a tip,
we're gonna cartwheel.
And if I hit
the water too fast,
we're done for sure.
Just tell me which way the
wind is blowing those swells.
Rich, turn the airplane.
We're gonna land parallel
to the swells.
We gotta come right
30 degrees. Confirm?
RICH: Confirmed.
Bug that heading for me.
Roger that.
2,000 feet. Airspeed 190.
You want flaps?
As much as you can give me.
Flaps at maximum.
1,000 feet. Airspeed 180.
Still too fast.
Airspeed 170.
Landing gear up.
APU fire suppression.
Watch your wings.
300 feet.
Airspeed still 170.
Ben...
move your seat
all the way back.
Tighten your harness.
Rich, keep that wing up.
I'm gonna bug you left
10 degrees.
Tail down.
Tail down. 100 feet.
Come on, girl, work with me.
Ben, move your seat
all the way back. Do it!
Brace for impact!
Oh, shit!
[METALLIC GROANING]
MAN 1: Help me!
MAN 2: Help!
Please!
MAN 3: Somebody!
MAN 2: Help!
Somebody!
Help!
Rich!
Wake up, Rich.
You did it.
If it wasn't
for that coral reef,
we'd be popping champagne
right now.
[CRACKING]
You okay?
Yeah.
[WOMEN CRYING]
Okay.
Hey! Hey.
You stay here, okay?
And I'll be right back.
Okay, okay.
Okay?
Oh, my God. Rich!
Grab him by the arms.
I'll try to get him loose,
okay?
One, two, three.
[GROANS] No, no, no!
Stop!
That's not going to work.
Hey.
You're gonna be okay, Rich.
We're gonna get you
out of here.
Guys, we don't have much time.
Easy, Rich. Your leg's pinned.
Crash ax.
PENNY: What?
Don't even think about it.
No, you're not taking my leg.
Not yet.
You can use it to pry me out.
[WOMAN SOBBING]
SAM: Lisa.
Lisa.
Lisa!
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[GASPING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Hey, little guy. Hey, hey.
[FINN WHIMPERING]
Okay? Yeah? Okay.
I have to get this off.
Okay. All right, all right.
You're okay.
Come here. Look at me.
It's okay. Yeah?
Hello? Anybody?
Hello?
Hello! Hello, anybody?
I'm here!
Hey.
Hold on.
Okay. Yeah.
FINN: Someone's here?
MAN: Someone here.
The nice lady.
She's gonna come.
She's gonna help us.
Yeah? She knows what to do.
ZOE: Okay.
Yeah.
[SHRIEKS]
[CRYING]
PENNY:
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
It's okay.
[GASPING]
It's not coming free.
You're losing a lot of blood.
[RUMBLING]
Guys, we have to move fast.
He's trapped.
There's no other way.
He's gonna bleed to death.
Ben, it's no good.
Don't be a chump.
Either way, I'm done
and I'm exactly
where I belong.
Don't give me that
"where I belong" crap.
You stay here, you die.
Get out. Both of you.
Lock the door.
If that's open
when this water breaks in,
we'll flood
the entire flight deck
and drag everybody
to the bottom.
I'm taking your leg.
You won't save any lives
by drowning in here
with some dickhead
who always refuses
to follow simple protocol.
It's your plane, Ben.
I'm not leaving you, Rich.
I'm not leaving you.
Confirm.
Confirmed.
Go home, Ben.
Be with your son.
PENNY: Thank you.
Ben, the ELT. Check the ELT.
Honey. Oh, honey.
It's okay.
Do you want to come
and sit down?
Penny.
Help me.
Lift her up.
[SHRIEKS]
You okay? Yeah?
Yeah.
Declan.
Declan. Declan, wake up!
Declan, wake up!
Shit.
What the fuck is happening?
Wait, are you all right?
The kids.
Fuck. We got to
get out of here.
No! Declan, don't!
♪ Fly me to the moon♪
♪ And let me play
among the stars♪
♪ Let me see
what spring is like♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars♪
♪ In other words♪
♪ Please be true♪
♪ I love you♪
What do we do?
Find survivors.
And get that ELT beacon.
MAN: Becky.
I think I've got a pulse.
Becky.
Come on.
Becky, wake up!
We have to move right now!
Becky!
Water's rising.
Can you move her?
She's, like, 150 pounds.
I've only got
the use of one arm
and I got to get
all the way up there?
150 pounds? Really?
I'm a...
grandmother.
The one I'm gonna help
is this little fellow here.
Let's go.
FINN: I can climb.
I'm a good climber.
Show us your stuff, hotshot.
Okay. Yep.
How long before they find us?
Could be an hour
or several hours.
That's if they got the signal.
"If"?
If the ELT activated
when we went down.
And if it didn't?
Yeah.
That's why I'm going
for a little swim.
It's in the midsection.
I'd take the raft,
but you might need it.
Let me go.
Waikiki Roughwater.
Three times.
I can do this, okay? Trust me.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
Um... To the middle
of the plane.
Are my mom and dad there?
I want to come.
Well, I have to swim,
sweetheart.
I can swim.
It's too far.
Okay? But I will look
for your parents, I promise.
And my little brother, Finn.
His name is Finn.
BEN: Penny.
When you get out there,
signal to confirm...
Okay.
...that the ELT is working,
all right?
This goes in the log, right?
Good enough for purser.
Chief Purser.
Here, take this.
No, it'll just slow me down.
Hey. Can you hold on to these
for me until I get back?
Thanks.
BEN: It's in the overhead,
starboard side, row 20.
Okay.
Just hit the switch and make
sure the light stays on, okay?
Hey, good luck.
We're gonna
find your family, Cora.
Okay?
You can do it, Becky.
Right behind you, hotshot.
It's this big lug
I'm worried about.
[CHUCKLES] Right. Great.
Now I got Shelley Winters
talking shit, huh?
BEN: Let me see that.
Hold still.
Put your hand here, okay?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir.
Shark.
Shark!
Shark! Penny!
Penny, shark!
Penny!
No!
Shark! Penny!
Penny! Shark!
Shark!
Put this on.
Wait, the shoes. The shoes.
Come on.
Keep your hands
out of the water.
[MAN GRUNTS]
No! Stop!
What?
Isn't this how we get out?
Deploy the raft?
We are in an air bubble.
Break the seal
and then we sink.
MAN: But...
Yeah, okay, okay. Yeah.
[WHISPERS] Five.
Sorry. Okay.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
CORA: Penny!
Penny! Shark!
Penny!
Shark in the water!
We're coming!
Penny!
Penny! Shark!
Help me!
Penny!
Penny! Penny, we're coming!
We're coming!
Come on! Give me your hand!
Penny.
[METALLIC CREAKING]
JIM: We're sinking.
HUTCH: Where the hell are we?
MAN: We are sinking.
JIM: What the...
You have a huge cut.
Let me help you.
It's nothing.
Swim to me! Swim to me!
Here. I've got you!
Come here.
Are you okay?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[FINN SOBBING]
How's that feel?
Less terrible.
Thank you for fixing me up.
And I'm sorry about
the door thing.
Yeah.
We are gonna be okay.
We've got to calm
this one down.
Otherwise we're gonna run
out of air, and terribly soon.
Hey, hey, little man.
You flying with your family?
My mommy and my new daddy
and my sister, Cora.
Okay, well, we're gonna
help you find your family.
I'm Matt. That's Becky.
And this is...
Zoe.
Zoe. Zoe.
And you are?
My name is Finn.
Finn.
[LOUD THUD]
It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be okay.
Stop saying that
when you know it's not true!
[FINN SOBBING]
We have to move back. Guys!
We have to move back.
Shut up, Esports.
What do you know
about anything?
There's too much
weight up here.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Help us.
Open your eyes, dumbass.
Can't you see
the steward's totally fried?
Just leave her alone, okay?
She's in shock.
Let me help you, okay?
Are you a doctor?
No, I'm a veterinarian.
DAN: Great.
Put a cone on her.
Stop her from licking herself.
See, that's why
I prefer animals to humans.
[RUMBLING]
We don't have much time.
Shut up. Just shut up.
SAM: We will sink.
We are all going to die!
HUTCH: What do you
expect us to do?
SAM: Move back.
To where?
In the water.
Take some weight off.
The kid's right.
There's a coral reef under us.
It might take
some pressure off it.
You go then.
One person
won't make a difference.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
What'd you just call me?
What did he call me?
All right, all right!
Knock it off, both of you.
COACH: Esport is right.
Now, come on.
Anybody else coming?
Huh?
HUTCH: Whoa!
Hold up, Jesse. What?
If this thing goes down,
anyone's who's down there
is gonna be stuck inside.
Okay?
Jesse, don't be stupid, bro.
Some of these wounded
and old people
won't make it out there, man.
Jesse, come back here. Jesse.
Let's go. Come on, come on.
Everyone's going.
Yeah, everyone's going.
Go for it.
COACH: Just breathe.
Guess you ain't getting me
that vodka soda anytime soon.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Coach!
COACH: I got you!
MARTINE: Are you hurt?
Lisa. Lisa.
Lisa! Lisa.
MARTINE: Is there anyone else?
HUTCH: Coach! Coach!
Coach!
No, no, no!
Grab him, Jesse! Grab him!
Move! Move!
Coach! Jesse!
Come on.
Hey, hey. Take it easy.
You.
Get in the water!
Take it easy. Take it easy.
MARTINE: No, stop.
Get in the water!
LISA: No!
Get in...
I didn't know!
Get in the water!
Stop it! Stop it!
LISA: [SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
Stop it! Stop it, please!
Stop it!
Hey! Hey!
How is this helping? Huh?
Do you want to live?
Do you?
Yes. Yes.
Then we need to keep our cool.
Tell me we're gonna
keep our cool.
I'm gonna keep my cool.
[LOW CREAKING]
BECKY: Kid, have some nuts.
Good protein.
Growing boys
need their protein.
Mommy says nuts make me fat.
What kind of a mother
would say a thing like that?
Okay, fine. Screw the nuts.
How old are you anyway?
How much air do you think
we have left?
FINN: Almost eight.
BECKY: You're seven.
It's too risky.
I presume fully potty-trained.
MATT:
What, so just do nothing?
ZOE: The doors stay shut.
How old do you think I am?
A hundred.
Pretty close.
Nobody is going to find us
if we stay in here.
[FINN CRYING]
Oh, great job, guys.
MATT: Huh?
It's already getting stuffy.
We could swim.
I can go first,
swim down and find a way out.
MATT: No.
No, not on my watch.
I can do it.
ZOE: I know the plane
better than you.
And you have a broken wrist.
Which you made better,
remember?
Here, strap it.
Come on.
We don't have much time.
Okay. So, I'm gonna
take a look around
and then I'm gonna be back
in a tick, okay?
Yeah? Yeah.
Okay. Good.
Don't go.
Hey, Finn.
You look after the ladies
for me while I'm gone, yeah?
Okay, okay, okay.
Hurry back...
Matt.
She remembered my name. Huh?
Look, I've got
a good feeling about us.
MATT: Hey, hey!
Hey, over here!
Help us!
Help! Over here!
There's people
that need help! Help!
My daughter, Cora.
[YELPING] Help!
Help!
WOMAN: How could this happen?
MAN: We're in the middle
of nowhere.
WOMAN: How do you just
fall out of the sky?
MAN 2:
How long till they rescue us?
WOMAN 2: Don't be a smart-ass.
Just answer the question.
Look, I'll tell you
what I know, okay?
Probably your fucking fault.
You and this shitty airline.
Look, you're angry,
you want answers.
You're gonna get them, okay?
Truth is, we're lucky
to be alive to blame somebody.
There were 257 souls
on this flight.
I count, maybe, 30 of us.
The way I see it,
we have one job to do,
and that is to get home
to see our families.
Okay, we have rafts.
We need to get in them.
If you don't have
a life jacket,
take one from under a seat.
Tell me your name.
I'm Hutch.
Hutch, I need you to pull out
that second raft.
Everybody, help Hutch
get the raft into the water.
HUTCH: It's stuck! It's stuck!
Here, hold on to that.
Cora, I need you
to stay here, okay?
Stay away from the edge,
all right?
Okay.
I'm gonna go get something.
Hey, everybody, be careful.
The tide is moving fast.
HUTCH: Two, there...
All right, here we go. Ready?
I think we got it.
All right, ready? Ready?
Daddy.
Daddy!
Hey, come back! We need this!
Let's go, let's go.
Go. Go, go, go. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
HUTCH: Anybody,
please, help me!
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Come on, baby.
We got this. Ready?
Go, go, go.
We got this. One, two, three!
Pull!
CORA: Daddy!
Cora!
HUTCH: Pull!
Get this onto a raft,
don't drop it.
CORA: Daddy!
Cora!
MAN: Let's get out of here.
Daddy, I'm sorry!
Cora! Cora! Come on.
I'm sorry!
Get away from there!
No, man, what are you doing?
Why didn't it open?
DAN: I don't know,
pull the goddamn rope!
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Come on, come on.
Come on.
Hey!
Here!
The ELT.
What?
The locator. That box
I gave you. Where is it?
You gotta be kidding me.
Come on, man,
I was counting on you.
All you had to do was
get it on the raft.
Yeah, well,
if it was so important,
maybe you should've
looked after it.
Locater?
What's he talking about?
Is that what they need
to find us?
And you lost it?
Hey, don't put this
on me, man.
This was your responsibility,
Captain.
SAM: Hey!
Over there!
Here!
Do you see them?
Please, do something.
No way.
No, they can swim
to the other raft.
The current is too strong.
They'll never make it.
Can't you see
we're already taking on water?
[HUTCH COUGHS]
Whoa... What... What...
Oh, my God!
Who the hell are you
to decide?
I'm the captain.
It's my plane.
Oh, that plane?
Great job. Huh?
People are dead
because of you.
And now you want
to risk our lives
to make yourself feel better?
No way. We stay put.
You call yourself
a captain, huh?
You can't even pilot a raft.
We're going to get them.
You know damn well
what will happen
to those two young men
if we don't.
Untether these rafts.
No!
Hey!
DAN: He hit me.
You're a witness.
Shut up, bitch.
You heard the lady.
And stop rocking the raft.
BEN: Let's go.
[FINN WHIMPERING]
I want to go.
How much longer
do we have to stay here?
I hope Matt hasn't swum away
with a mermaid.
He wouldn't leave us.
[METALLIC CREAKING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What's it waiting for?
[WHISPERS]
[SAM SHUSHES]
[GRUNTING]
SAM: Let's get out of here.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
[BOTH PANTING]
You two again, huh?
All right,
let's get out of here.
Let's go.
When we get outside the plane,
we inflate our jackets.
They'll take us
straight up to the surface
like a big balloon.
No, I need a little more time.
You can't stay here.
I can't take both of you.
You can do it.
BECKY: Doing this, doing that.
I'm always trying
to keep doing.
Ever since Bill died,
it just gets old, you know?
Becky, I'm sorry. I am.
But we have to go now.
No, I know. You take Finn.
No! You come, too. Please.
You stay strong, hotshot.
I admire your style.
Don't worry about me.
I will come back, Becky.
I promise.
You okay? Yeah?
Good boy.
[METAL CREAKING]
[GASPS]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
[SOBBING]
Matt!
ZOE: We can make it.
DAN: So, Captain,
do you have a plan
that doesn't rely
on just dumb luck?
You know, we're alive.
We're all alive.
You got kids?
Yeah.
My daughter, Terri.
My little boy, Sean.
DAN: Well, I got three.
Youngest is five.
I can tell you they ain't
growing up without me.
So, whatever you gotta do
to make yourself
feel better about
losing all those
people back there...
but don't use me, pal.
Because I'm going home...
whatever it takes.
Yeah, I am sure your kids
are real proud of you.
[SCOFFS]
No wonder you're single.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] A plane!
Plane is here.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Down here, you asshole!
Hey!
Did they see us?
They saw us, all right.
We just gotta hold on.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ZOE SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS] Zoe!
[FINN SOBBING]
[PANTING]
Zoe!
Zoe, wake up!
Somebody help!
[THUDS]
[WHIMPERING]
[BECKY BREATHING HEAVILY]
My dear little Bella.
I don't know
why I'm doing this.
You're never going to hear me.
There's no service.
Bella...
I'm going to have
a little chat with God...
and ask him to fill your life
with as much...
joy...
as you've given me.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
Guam, Red Tail 24.
Any updates
on the transport situation?
MAN: Working on it.
We've got a Chinese trawler
in the area.
Red Tail 24, standby.
PILOT: Copy that.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] This is
the Xing Yang Yuan Yu 08.
MAN: Captain, we are enacting
the 1974 SOLAS convention.
There's been
a commercial airliner crash.
Your ship is closest
to the area
where we believe
there are survivors
in need of assistance.
Copy, Commander.
What?
Thank you.
Just tell her.
That you're crazy about her.
SAM: I can't break team rules.
What team rule?
Players cannot date
each other.
My God.
You're such an idiot.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
No one listens to that rule.
Just tell her.
BEN: Hey, Cora.
Drink this.
They're not here.
Hey.
They left me.
Come on.
They didn't leave you.
My dad told me to look
after my little brother.
I was horrible.
I don't hate him.
I know.
He's seven.
My son is seven.
That's Sean,
there on the right.
He's not seven.
It's an old picture.
Hmm?
They'll never get to see
how I turn out.
Hey, they'll know.
Parents always know.
They're always with you, Cora.
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
Oh, yes. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
MAN: Oh, hey.
Oh, my God.
They're gonna rescue us.
Hutch, look after Cora.
Over here!
Hey, we're here!
Guam, Red Tail 24,
we have survivors.
Dropping flares and putting
swimmer in the water.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Hey!
Deploy swimmer.
No!
WOMAN: We're at the door.
PILOT: Copy that. Good to go.
No!
We see you.
I can't pull us up.
Up, up, up!
MAN: Red Tail 24,
everything all right?
WOMAN: Oh, my God!
[ALARM BLARING]
Cut it loose. Cut it loose!
DAN: Get me out!
Get me out of the water!
Give me your hand.
Get me out!
Get me out of here!
No!
Bastard!
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
Hey!
I'm here!
[HORN BLOWING]
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Why'd they stop?
Why'd they stop?
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
They can't get past the reef.
We need to go to them.
How?
Where are the paddles?
We don't have any paddles.
We have no paddles.
DAN: So what now, Captain?
The current will carry us
to the deep water.
Hey!
HUTCH: The other rafts,
they've got paddles.
They'll make it.
Where's Cora?
The little girl.
Cora? Cora? Cora?
Is she in the water?
Cora?
There she is! There!
Look, look!
Hey!
Cora!
JIM: Cora, stay there!
Cora.
MARTINE: Cora!
We have to go get her.
The current's too strong.
DAN: Well, the other raft's
nearly there.
BEN: That plane's going to be
in the water in 15 minutes.
All right, I'm gonna get her.
HUTCH: The sharks.
Are you crazy?
They're everywhere.
No, it's your boat.
HUTCH: Hey, no, wait!
No.
HUTCH: Swim fast! Swim faster!
SAM: He can make it.
LISA: He's gonna make it.
Help me!
I am an American!
He made it!
Yes!
Cora, hey.
Cora, look at me.
Hey.
Cora, we're gonna go
for a swim.
Together. You and me.
I want to stay here
with my daddy.
You can't stay here, Cora.
We gotta take
a little detour, okay?
The water's rising, Cora.
Your daddy wants you
to be a brave girl, okay?
All right,
let's put this on you.
Okay? There you go.
We're gonna be
all right, Cora.
We got this, okay?
I'm gonna put this belt on
over my neck,
around my back, okay?
And I want you to hold onto it
while we swim. All right?
You're not gonna
let go of this, okay?
You hold on tight.
Okay.
Hey, we're drifting away.
We're drifting away,
we're drifting away from them.
DAN: Wrong way, dumbass.
To the boat!
Grab the belt, Cora. Grab it.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
[CORA SCREAMING]
[IN ENGLISH] Shark! Shark!
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
CORA: They all left.
Why'd they go?
God only knows.
MARTINE: It's okay, it's okay.
Everything's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
JIM: I think they're gone.
MARTINE: We'll be okay.
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
Yeah.
[LIGHTER CLINKS]
You son of a bitch.
JIM: Oh, my God!
[DAN SCREAMING]
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Here, Cora.
Let's put this around you.
A little detour. Huh?
Yeah.
A little detour.
MARTINE: Hey!
Hey, we got a signal.
JIM: We got reception.
Ben, we got reception!
The phones are working!
The pet chip. Your phone?
Can you see your phone?
Can I see it?
Password's his birthday.
[BEEPING]
There. See?
BEN: Thank you, Captain.
We owe your crew for
everything you've done for us.
Thank you.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Raft. Over there.
CORA: Where's my brother?
He's gotta be here.
The tracker says he's here.
Finn?
I'm sorry, Cora.
Finn.
[GASPS]
CORA: Finn! Finn!
Zoe!
Finn!
Finn, Finn!
ZOE: We made it.
Cora!
Finn! Finn!
BEN: Come on. There you go.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Cora.
Becky? Becky?
She's waiting for me.
BEN: Come on,
let's get her up.
[SNIFFLING]
[LINE RINGING]
NADINE: Ben?
It's me.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
[CRYING]
Yeah.
I thought we lost you.
I'm okay.
Ben...
SEAN: Let me talk to him!
NADINE: Sean... Oh, my God.
SEAN: Dad's on the phone
right now.
Daddy, are you there?
I'm here, Sean.
I'm right here.
SEAN: Where are you?
I'm coming home.
SEAN: Mom, he's coming home.
He's coming home!
NADINE: I told you
he would, darling.
SEAN: I love you, Dad.
BEN: I love you, too, son.
I love all of you.